The first high heel ever
was a piece of military footwear.
第一个高跟鞋是一件军用鞋
西亚人民曾是伟大的骑马者，这就是他们的战斗方式
People in West Asia had been
tremendous horse riders,
西亚人民曾是伟大的骑马者，这就是他们的战斗方式
and that's how they fought, they rode
in the saddle and they stood up
西亚人民曾是伟大的骑马者，这就是他们的战斗方式
and that's how they fought, they rode
in the saddle and they stood up
他们骑在马鞍上，站起来拍摄弓箭，这意味着
to shoot their bows and that meant
you need a heel to keep
他们骑在马鞍上，站起来拍摄弓箭，这意味着
to shoot their bows and that meant
you need a heel to keep
您需要脚后跟，以使马in保持良好状态并稳定
you in the stirrups, nice and stable.
The Shah of Persia,
he's called Abbas the First,
您需要脚后跟，以使马in保持良好状态并稳定
The Shah of Persia,
he's called Abbas the First,
波斯，他第一次派人叫阿巴斯
he sends off some emissaries
into Europe and they turn up
波斯，他第一次派人叫阿巴斯
he sends off some emissaries
into Europe and they turn up
一些使者进入欧洲，他们穿着高跟鞋出现，每个人
wearing high heels
and everyone goes...
一些使者进入欧洲，他们穿着高跟鞋出现，每个人
wearing high heels
and everyone goes...
突然间，这种军事服装在欧洲被采用
...so suddenly this military clothing
becomes adopted in Europe.
突然间，这种军事服装在欧洲被采用
但是到了1600年代初期，我们才开始看到鳗鱼
But it's a little bit later on,
in the early 1600s, that we start
但是到了1600年代初期，我们才开始看到鳗鱼
to see heels coming in,
and it starts with the blokes,
但是到了1600年代初期，我们才开始看到鳗鱼
to see heels coming in,
and it starts with the blokes,
进来，它始于家伙，这是男子气概，但什么
it's for being manly and butch.
But what happens quite quickly
进来，它始于家伙，这是男子气概，但什么
it's for being manly and butch.
But what happens quite quickly
发生得很快，就是女性开始效仿男性时尚，其中一部分是
is women start to emulate
male fashion, and part of that
发生得很快，就是女性开始效仿男性时尚，其中一部分是
is they start wearing men's shoes.
The real big moment is when Louis XIV
发生得很快，就是女性开始效仿男性时尚，其中一部分是
is they start wearing men's shoes.
The real big moment is when Louis XIV
他们开始穿男鞋真正重要的时刻是法国的路易十四
of France starts wearing heels,
because he's quite a small man,
他们开始穿男鞋真正重要的时刻是法国的路易十四
of France starts wearing heels,
because he's quite a small man,
开始穿高跟鞋，因为他是个矮个子，而且有名的红色
and he famously has red heels
- that Louboutin mirrored
开始穿高跟鞋，因为他是个矮个子，而且有名的红色
and he famously has red heels
- that Louboutin mirrored
Louboutin的高跟鞋后来面世
later on in the 20th Century.
20世纪突然，法庭上的每个人都穿着高跟鞋
Suddenly everyone at the court
is wearing heels.
20世纪突然，法庭上的每个人都穿着高跟鞋
Heels go through a bit
of an up and down history
20世纪突然，法庭上的每个人都穿着高跟鞋
Heels go through a bit
of an up and down history
经历了一段上下的历史和1700年，我们很多人都在谈论
and the 1700s, philosophers are
talking about the rationalism of men,
经历了一段上下的历史和1700年，我们很多人都在谈论
and the 1700s, philosophers are
talking about the rationalism of men,
相比之下，男人的理性主义被认为是情感上的，
by contrast, women are said
to be emotional and sentimental
相比之下，男人的理性主义被认为是情感上的，
by contrast, women are said
to be emotional and sentimental
感性的，不能被信任去做重要的事情，例如思考，所以男人
and can't be trusted to do
important things like think.
感性的，不能被信任去做重要的事情，例如思考，所以男人
And so men are being advised
to wear rational shoes
感性的，不能被信任去做重要的事情，例如思考，所以男人
And so men are being advised
to wear rational shoes
建议人们穿合理的鞋子和高跟鞋，而不是合理的1860年代
and high heels are not rational.
The 1860s, this is when women's
heels start to become sexy.
建议人们穿合理的鞋子和高跟鞋，而不是合理的1860年代
The 1860s, this is when women's
heels start to become sexy.
这是女人的高跟鞋开始变得性感的时候，我们有了崭新的摄影作品
We have photography,
a brand new technology,
这是女人的高跟鞋开始变得性感的时候，我们有了崭新的摄影作品
We have photography,
a brand new technology,
技术，而且经常看到这段时期的色情内容
and quite often
in pornography of this period,
技术，而且经常看到这段时期的色情内容
you're seeing women
still wearing their boots,
技术，而且经常看到这段时期的色情内容
you're seeing women
still wearing their boots,
女人仍然穿着靴子，脚跟穿上鞋子，所以它变得
their shoes with the heels on,
so it becomes erotic.
女人仍然穿着靴子，脚跟穿上鞋子，所以它变得
their shoes with the heels on,
so it becomes erotic.
好色之徒
好莱坞对希尔斯（Hills）的崛起产生了巨大的影响，成为好莱坞性感的象征。
Hollywood had a huge influence
on the rise of heels as the symbol
好莱坞对希尔斯（Hills）的崛起产生了巨大的影响，成为好莱坞性感的象征。
of sexiness. In the 1950s,
Marilyn Monroe famously quoted,
好莱坞对希尔斯（Hills）的崛起产生了巨大的影响，成为好莱坞性感的象征。
of sexiness. In the 1950s,
Marilyn Monroe famously quoted,
1950年代的玛丽莲·梦露（Marilyn Monroe）著名地引用了B公司的确切字眼，但她说你
I can't think of the exact words
but she said you know...
1950年代的玛丽莲·梦露（Marilyn Monroe）著名地引用了B公司的确切字眼，但她说你
I can't think of the exact words
but she said you know...
知道我们欠了这么多发明高跟鞋的男人，她在讲
...she was speaking on behalf of
women. For Monroe, who was about
知道我们欠了这么多发明高跟鞋的男人，她在讲
...she was speaking on behalf of
women. For Monroe, who was about
代表梦露（Monroe）的女性，她们讲述魅力，美丽和性感
glamour and beauty and sexiness,
she felt that that was an asset.
代表梦露（Monroe）的女性，她们讲述魅力，美丽和性感
glamour and beauty and sexiness,
she felt that that was an asset.
她觉得那是一种资产[音乐]
谁能说出女人是否穿着高跟鞋而实际上却看不见她们
People can tell whether women are
wearing high heels without actually
谁能说出女人是否穿着高跟鞋而实际上却看不见她们
seeing their feet, so it is that
posture, change in the gait.
谁能说出女人是否穿着高跟鞋而实际上却看不见她们
seeing their feet, so it is that
posture, change in the gait.
脚是门的姿势改变，但是最近的一项研究表明
But a more recent study has shown
that actually it's changing the shape
脚是门的姿势改变，但是最近的一项研究表明
But a more recent study has shown
that actually it's changing the shape
实际上，实际上是脊柱形状的变化
of the spine that is actually
the attractive thing.
实际上，实际上是脊柱形状的变化
of the spine that is actually
the attractive thing.
有吸引力的东西
我们看了所有关于高跟鞋的研究，但它们并不健康，嘿
We looked at all the research on
high heels and they are not healthy,
我们看了所有关于高跟鞋的研究，但它们并不健康，嘿
there was increased risk of
musculoskeletal conditions,
我们看了所有关于高跟鞋的研究，但它们并不健康，嘿
there was increased risk of
musculoskeletal conditions,
肌肉骨骼疾病，拇囊炎和疼痛的风险增加
bunions and pain.
[音乐]
[音乐]我在那儿-我有点太守旧了
I think they're too iconic and too
much a part of aesthetics and imagery
[音乐]我在那儿-我有点太守旧了
I think they're too iconic and too
much a part of aesthetics and imagery
历史，力量和性爱中美学和意象的一部分
and history and power
and sex to ever go away,
历史，力量和性爱中美学和意象的一部分
and history and power
and sex to ever go away,
走了，我想他们会一直在那里，我宁愿背诵痛苦和磨难
and I think they'll always be there.
I'd rather go through quite a lot of
pain and wear them and look nice,
走了，我想他们会一直在那里，我宁愿背诵痛苦和磨难
I'd rather go through quite a lot of
pain and wear them and look nice,
他们看起来不错，我想我为此感到疯狂，我想我们都知道
and suffer for it, I think.
I'm crazy about fashion,
I think we all are.
他们看起来不错，我想我为此感到疯狂，我想我们都知道
And I think any smart woman
would go on wearing them,
他们看起来不错，我想我为此感到疯狂，我想我们都知道
And I think any smart woman
would go on wearing them,
我认为任何一口聪明的井都会在任何地方继续前进，无论
irrespective of what
the consequences are.
我认为任何一口聪明的井都会在任何地方继续前进，无论
irrespective of what
the consequences are.
结果是
感谢收看，别忘了订阅并单击保释金以接收
Thanks for watching. Don't forget to subscribe and click the bell to receive notifications for new videos.
新视频的通知很快就会再见
See you again soon!